All right. It's a new day.
All that stuff about Rachel,
you don't feel that now.
It was crazy. You're fine.
You're better than fine.
You are,
as your friend Tony would say
Grrreat!
Everything's normal.
She's just your friend Rachel.
Your friend Rachel.
Hi, sweetie.
Hey, it's your
girlfriend Rachel!
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hi.
Are you... are you high?
I just had
the most amazing bath.
Really?
I don't like baths.
Wait, you like
them with me.
Honey, it's not the bath
I enjoy.
It's the wet, naked lady.
( sighs )
Baths are so relaxing.
Really? What do you do?
You just sit in there stewing
in your own filth.
How dirty do you think I am?
I'm telling you
if you had some candles and
some bubbles and some music
you would love it.
It would take all
of your stress away.
Honey, it's 2:00 on a Wednesday,
and I'm watching Road Rules.
How stressed do you think I am?
Hey, Chandler.
Hey.
You got a minute?
I really need to talk to you.
Oh, uh, yeah.
Is this a cold pizza talk
or a leftover meat loaf talk?
Well, neither.
Oh, my God, what's up?
I don't know.
It's just...
Lately, I've been feeling...
Okay, here's what it is.
You know what?
I feel a lot better, thanks.
No, no, no.
Just come back.
All right.
Um...
You and Monica,
friends for a long time
and sure, there are rules.
But then you went to London.
No, but that's different.
I mean, there are rules
there, too.
You know what I mean?
Do you?
It was different for you guys.
I mean, you were both
in the same place, right?
In London?
Yeah.
Yes, when Monica
and I were in London
we were both in London.
You know what,
this is a bad idea.
Forget it.
Forget all about it.
And listen, do me a favor,
this conversation--
between you and me.
If that.
Hi. Oh, Ross,
don't forget
we have that doctor's
appointment tomorrow.
Right.
Hey, you going to find out
the sex of the baby?
No, no. We talked about it,
and we don't want to know.
All we care about is that
it's happy and healthy.
Yup, happy and healthy
and cute.
And smart.
And popular.
With an aptitude
for science.
Are you two talking
about the same baby?
Hey, have you started
thinking of names yet?
Oh, yeah.
I've come up with
a bunch of ideas.
Really? Me, too.
Me, too!
Really?
Uh-huh.
If it's a girl, Phoebe,
and if it's a boy, Phoebo.
Maybe. But it wouldn't hurt
to have a backup, you know?
Uh, Rach, Rach,
what were you thinking?
Okay. Um, I was thinking,
if it's a girl, how about...
Sandrine? It's French.
Huh.
That's a really pretty name
for an industrial solvent.
( clears throat )
Okay, fine.
What do you have?
All right,
it's for a boy.
I know it's
a little out there, but...
Darwin.
Wow.
My God, our child
will be beaten to death
in the schoolyard.
Yeah, by Sandrine.
You're just saying that
'cause I said no to your name.
I'm really, really not.
How about you each
get five vetoes?
All right.
That sounds fair.
All right. Yeah.
I don't think you're going
to need it, though.
Okay, check this out.
If it's a girl, Rain.
Veto.
Why?
Rain? "Hi, hi,
my name is Rain.
"I have my own kiln
and my dress is made
out of wheat."
I know her!
I bought homemade soap from her
at a Dead show.
Okay, how about
for a guy, Thatcher?
Ross, why do you
hate our child?
Fine, you go.
Okay. James.
Huh.
But only if it's a girl.
Oh, veto.
Uh, how about...
Ooh, I like Ruth.
What about Ruth?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are we having
an 89-year-old?
How about Dayton?
Veto. Stewart?
Veto. Sawyer?
Veto. Helen?
Veto.
Is it me
or is "veto" starting
to sound really good?
Hey.
Boy, do I have
a surprise for you.
Sex on the balcony?
No, but someone's
really not going
to get over that
idea, are they?
What is it?
I drew you a bath.
Honey, I don't like baths.
Could you draw me a picture
of us having sex on the balcony?
Please, will you
just try it for me?
Come on, I used
all my best stuff.
I lit some candles,
I put on some music.
I used bath salts
plus bubble bath.
And got you this
little plastic navy ship.
So it's a boy bath.
Well, this does
butch it up a bit.
I swear, if you try it,
you will love it.
All right, if I do this
can we at least discuss
sex on the balcony?
Absolutely.
Bet I know how
that discussion's going to go.
( soft music playing )
Oh, this isn't so bad.
I like the flower smell.
Which is okay,
because I've got my boat.
( knocking )
So?
Oh, my God.
I told you
you were a bath person.
Hey, when you get out,
maybe I can give you a facial.
I'm going to need a bigger boat.
I don't think you had
an open mind
about the name Ruth.
I mean, come on.
Little Ruthie Gellar?
How cute is that?
Oh, oh, my God.
I can practically hear
the mahjong tiles.
DOCTOR:
Okay.
All your tests look fine.
Now, are you two
interested in knowing
the sex of the baby?
Uh, no. No, we're not.
But you have it right there
in that file?
You could tell us
whether it's a boy or a girl?
Dayton or Sandrine?
Phoebe or Phoebo?
That's right.
But if you don't want to know...
No, no, we want
to wait, right?
Right. Right.
( beeping )
Oh, I'll be right back.
And, uh, I know
it's really not my place
but please don't name
your child Phoebo.
So, which of these babies
do you think
is the ugliest?
What?
Rach, come on.
That's terrible.
They're, uh, they're babies.
They're all beautiful.
Third one from the left?
Yeah, why is it staring at me?
I think it knows
I'm talking about it.
Don't-don't you...
Wha... wha?!
What?!
You're looking!
I didn't.
I saw you!
Okay, fine, I did.
But I didn't see anything,
I swear.
Shame on you!
Ugly baby judges you!
Okay, but, Ross,
just listen to me...
No, no, no, no!
Don't tell me!
I don't want to know!
But I couldn't
even if I wanted to
because I don't know.
I swear, I didn't see anything,
and I don't want to know.
It was just a momentary lapse.
Momentary lapse.
Don't you have any self-control?
Okay, a couple months late
on the lecture, Ross.
Hello?
CHANDLER:
I'm in the bathroom.
Can you come in here?
I think there's
something wrong.
You know what?
I think I'll wait out here.
I'm in the bathtub.
Oh.
Hey, what's wrong?
I drew my own bath,
but I did it wrong.
The water's tepid,
the salt didn't dissolve
and is now... lodged places.
And the scents I used
don't complement each other.
Eucalyptus and chamomile?
Oh!
What?
The bath salts...
they're starting to effervesce.
It's different.
It's interesting.
Okay, let's talk
about something else.
Yeah, sure, sure.
So, what was going on
with you today?
Oh-oh-oh!
Well, I actually
had the weirdest
conversation with Joey.
He was talking about rules
and right and wrong and...
I had the exact same
conversation.
You did? What was
he talking about?
I don't know, Joey hasn't had
this much trouble
getting out words
since we saw him in Macbeth.
Uh. That was a long night.
All right,
let's break this down.
What exactly did he say to you?
Okay. He was talking
about rules
and looking at people
differently.
He didn't say anything
about that to me.
What'd he tell you?
He was asking
all these questions
about you, me and London,
and, of course
the glue that holds
this all together, the rules.
Okay, so you, me and London,
looking at people differently.
Maybe he wants to do
what you and I did in London
with someone.
But what did he mean by "rules"?
Wait a minute.
He stopped talking
the minute Phoebe came in.
Because he was looking
at her differently.
And Phoebe is his friend
so he thinks that would be
breaking the rules.
My God! He wants to do it
with Phoebe in London!
PHOEBE:
You guys?
Just a minute.
That's Mrs. Tribbiani.
You don't say anything.
Why would I say anything?
That two of our best friends
could start
the greatest love affair
of their lives
and they would have me to thank
and then we could all start
having babies?
I'm not going
to let you say anything.
You just stay here.
Oh, God!
Oh, hey, Monica,
I brought back your iron.
Oh, you had that?
I thought I lost it.
I got a new one,
like, a month ago.
Oh, just as well.
I broke this one.
What?
Nothing.
Okay.
I mean, I really shouldn't say.
I mean, I'm really
not supposed to.
Fine.
It's a humdinger.
Well, then it's really too bad
that you can't tell me.
Somebody likes you.
( groans )
Is it Chandler?
No.
Well, then tell him
to stop staring.
It's Joey.
Really? Joey?
You don't say.
Is it something
you'd be interested in?
I don't know, I don't know,
I don't know.
You know, I mean,
on the one hand
Mother, may I?
But on the other hand...
No. No, I can't.
We're friends. No. Oh, no.
I don't want to risk
what we have.
I guess that makes sense.
So, you think you're going
to talk to him?
Sure, yeah.
I mean, it's Joey.
I don't want him
to get hurt.
Well, I must say
I am on fire.
First Chandler, now Joey.
No, no. Not Chandler,
just Joey.
Sure.
Hi.
Hey.
You know what?
I've been thinking about it.
I'm really coming around
on the name Ruth.
I think I would actually
consider naming our child that.
Rach, I can't tell you
how much that means to me.
Oh...
Wait a minute.
You-you hated the name Ruth.
Why... why would you
change your mind?
Unless...
you know we're never
going to have to use it.
You did see the folder.
You know it's a boy!
I didn't see anything.
I actually changed my mind
about the name.
Oh, I don't think so.
You're just giving me Ruth
so you'll get to name
him when it's a boy.
And then that's when
you'll swoop in
and name him Heath
or Blaine or... Sequoia.
I would... Sequoia?
Veto.
Fine.
( laughs sarcastically )
Unless...
( groans )
you anticipated that
I would figure all this out
and you know that it actually
is a girl, and...
and you really do want
her to be named Ruth.
Well, I'm not
falling for that!
Okay, Ruth is
off the table!
But, Ross,
you want the name Ruth.
Not like this.
Hey.
Well, what's up?
Um, Joey, I know.
What?
I know.
What...?
I know about
your feelings.
Oh, my God. You do?
Yes, and I'm sorry.
I know things worked out
for Chandler and Monica
but that's very rare.
I know, I know.
And this is so much
more complicated
than it was for those guys.
I mean, it's Rachel,
for God sakes.
For God sakes, it's Rachel!
I know, I know.
And she's not only
my friend
she's my pregnant friend.
She's my pregnant friend
who's Ross's ex.
Yeah, that's Rachel.
Beat me over the head with it.
What... what am
I going to do?
You know, and I keep trying
to get rid of these feelings,
you know?
I stayed up all last night
and made a list of everything
I don't like about her.
You want to hear it?
Yeah.
She made me switch
to light mayo.
That's it! That's all I got!
And you know what?
Tastes the same,
and my pants fit better.
Joey, I think you're just
getting upset for nothing.
This is probably just a crush.
You think?
Absolutely.
You know, you get
this rush of feelings
but then it goes away.
Yeah, just a crush.
That's all this is.
It's a crush.
I'm Joey. I don't
get deep feelings.
That's right.
There you go.
Yeah, crushes happen
all the time.
I know I've had them
for all you guys.
Well, except
for Ross and Chandler.
Well...
You know...
and I'm sure
you've had them for us.
Not really.
Mm-hmm.
Throw me a bone here.
So, I, uh... I
called the doctor
and now we both know
the sex of the baby.
What?
That's right.
The student has
become the master.
Ross, I swear, I don't know.
Oh, come on, you
know it's a girl.
A what?
You... you really
didn't know?
We're having a girl?
No.
That's what you just said.
You said girl.
Yes. I'm... I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm not.
We're having a girl!
Sometimes I can't
believe it's with you.
But still...
we're having a girl!
Oh!
I know. I know.
You know what?
I'm putting Ruth
back on the table.
Oh... yes, we'll have ourselves
a little baby Ruth.
Permission to veto.
Yes, please.
Hey.
Do I smell essential oils?
Yeah, I'm going to take a bath.
I was just going to get
a magazine.
Okay.
What do you think
you're doing?
Leaving my troubles behind?
All right, look, I know
that you're new at this
but this is completely
unacceptable bath decorum.
Oh, it's so hard to care
when you're this relaxed.
Okay, fine.
You can have the bath
but I am taking your boat.
Now you're just a girl in a tub.
Ooh... oh.
Hey!
Hi, Bubbles. Manly.
Well, I just thought
I would drop by
and let you know
how it went with Joey.
You told her?!
She pulled it out of me.
She's like
a conversational wizard.
How did it go?
Well, you were wrong.
He doesn't like me.
What?
Yeah.
How would you like it if
I sent you to Lee Majors' house
and I told you
that he liked you
and you went down there,
and you found out
that he didn't like you--
how would you feel?
I don't think I'd care.
Really? Lee Majors is hot.
JOEY:
Hello?
We're in the bathroom.
Why?
Because it's a relaxing
and enjoyable time.
What are guys doing in here?
Oh, my God.
A friend he's looking
at differently
but it's wrong...
it's Rachel.
You like Rachel?!
Look, it's no big deal, okay?
Phoebe and I talked about it.
It's just a crush.
It's going to go away.
Dude, you got to rearrange
your bubbles. Whoa.
Mazel tov.
Yeah.
Hey. Ooh... Hi.
Hey.
Ross and I were
looking for you.
What are we all
doing in here?
Oh, my.
Honey, cover it
up with the boat.
ROSS:
Hello?
Yes, we're all in here, and
we'd love for you to join us.
Hi.
Well, hey...
what's going on?
Ooh, cool boat.
Oh, no.
Hey, did you tell them?
No, I was
waiting for you.
Tell us what?
We're having a girl.
Oh, wow! Really?
( all talking excitedly )
I'll get you later.
All right, it's a new day, and
it's just a crush, that's all.
Just a little crush.
All that worrying I was doing--
that was crazy... crazy!
Like my friend the bird here
would say
"It was cuckoo."
Everything's going to be fine.
It's just a crush.
Hi, sweetie.
I love you.
It's nice to do this
together, isn't it?
Yeah.
And what you're doing
feels so good.
I'm not touching you.
You're not?
It's the salts.
Oh, sweet Lord,
new realms of pleasure.
Whatever keeps you
off the balcony, big guy.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org